DEVIN HAMID UI DESIGNER

Contact

206-919-2267

devinhamid1@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/devin-hamid

www.behance.net/devinhamid

Shoreline, WA, USA

Skills & Tools

- Communication
- Teamworking
- Figma
- Adobe XD
- · Adobe Lightroom
- · Microsoft Office Suite
- Basic HTML and CSS
- Basic SQL
- Medidata Rave

Education

UI Design Certificate

With Frontend Development for Designers

2023 | CareerFoundry

Bachelor of Arts (Honors)

Theatre Performance and Direction. **Communication Minor** 2000 | Boise State University

About

UI Designer with a background in clinical trial form design as well as theatre arts. Collaborate with stakeholders to ensure optimal user experience in order to collect the most thorough and accurate data. Leverage an eye for design and an attention to detail for all types of business design needs.

Projects

OL Reign | Team App Redesign

UI Designer - CareerFoundry Project February - March 2023

- Designed high fidelity mock-ups for a redesign of the app for the OL Reign soccer team, enabling users to easily manage match tickets and access information.
- · Mock-ups designed to meet iOS and Android mobile guidelines.

Spot Finder | Location-Based Recommendation App

UX/UI Designer - CareerFoundry Project November 2022 - February 2023

- · Conceptualized and designed a responsive web app for dog owners by conducting user interviews, testing, and compiling resulting data to create high fidelity mock-ups of screens at multiple breakpoints.
- · User-centered design process and mobile-first approach were applied throughout.

Relevant Work History

Cancer Research and Biostatistics

Project Specialist / Case Report Form Designer 2009 - present

- · Define project requirements and write specifications while leading study builds in Electronic Data Capture (EDC) systems.
- Maintain accurate documentation and act as liaison between research study stakeholders and application developers.
- Projects are carefully documented and kept on schedule so stakeholders receive timely, accurate data that can improve cancer treatments.

Cancer Research and Biostatistics

Data Coordinator

2006 - 2009

· Performed quality control review of study data while acting as a reference resource to personnel at research study sites, ensuring data accuracy.

Actor

2000 - 2006

· Performed and taught theatre at various locations around the country.